Guide to the Planned Community Archives collection, 1960-2009
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Planned Community Archives collection
1960-2009
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
Planned Community Archives, Inc.
C0001
175.5 linear feet 351 boxes)
The collection consists of a variety of materials relating to planned communities across the United States with a particular emphasis on the planned community of Reston, Virginia, and international communities as well. The collection includes, correspondence, reports, promotional material, community brochures, newspapers, videotapes, slides, photographs and architectural drawings and blueprints. The collection is divided into 11 series in 351 boxes and 3 mapcases and is dated from 1960 to 2009.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Donated by the Planned Community Archives, Inc. in 1986 with additional donations in the years following.
Historical Information
The era of new town development in the United States, which is of special interest to Planned Community Archives (PCA), begins with the Greenbelt towns developed by the federally sponsored Works Progress Administration during the Great Depression of the 1930s. The next major new town development was Reston, Virginia, in 1962. Since that time, at least thirty-eight planned communities have been developed throughout the United States. Thirteen of these communities were sponsored by the Federal New Communities Program of the U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (1970 - 1983).
The records contained in this collection were assembled by the Planned Community Archives, Inc., of Reston, Virginia, and placed on deposit in Special Collections and Archives of Fenwick Library, George Mason University beginning in 1986. Each year since then has seen major additions to the collection. After many years of housing and processing the collection, George Mason University Libraries accepted the Planned Community Archives collections as a donation by Planned Community Archives, Inc.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of a variety of materials relating to planned communities across the United States with a particular emphasis on the planned community of Reston, Virginia and international communities as well. The collection includes, correspondence, reports, promotional material, community brochures, newspapers, videos, slides, photographs and architectural drawings and blueprints.
Series one is titled Reston and is divided into nine subseries. The information in this series contains correspondence, finance, plans, reports, meetings, publications, marketing, a scrapbook and general information. All of the information relates to the community of Reston in Virginia. There is additional Reston information in series nine, ten and eleven. The series is dated from 1961-2006 and is contained in boxes 1-42.
Series two is titled United States Planned Communities. The material in this series relates to planned communities in the United States other than Reston, such as Columbia, Maryland, Evergreen Mills, Hawaii, Portland and others. The series is comprised of correspondence, plans, reports and other paperwork relating to the development of these communities. The series dated from 1970 to 1996 and is contained in boxes 42-53.
Series three is titled International Planned Communities. The material in this series relates to international planned communities in countries such as France, Great Britain, Israel, China and others. The materials are mostly promotional from the communities and other information regarding the development of the communities. Some of the material is in the foreign language while others are printed in English. The series is dated from 1960 to 1990 and is contained in boxes 53-56.
Series four is titled Reports. The documents are reports from and about different communities, relating financial, environmental and other issues. There are also documents from the Federal government pertaining to the development of the communities. The series is dated from 1965 to 2001 and is contained in boxes 56-61.
Series five is titled Planed Community Archive Board. The series is small and contains the meeting minutes and other information from the board that created the planned community archive. The series dated from 1985 to 2001 and is contained in boxes 61-64.
Series six is titled Promotional Material. The series has promotional material from different planned communities such as pamphlets, flyers, articles and others. The series dated from 1966 to 1990 and is contained in boxes 64-66.
Series seven is titled Brochures. The series is comprised of different planned communities brochures, such as Arbor Glenn, Fairfield, Key West, Ridgewood and many others. The series dated in the 1990s and is contained in boxes 66-75.
Series eight is titled Newspapers. The series is comprised of copies of The Connection a newspaper from Reston. The Connection, the local newspaper has articles mostly about local events. For example there are articles about Reston Association elections, local residents and also the Washington Redskins. There are additional copies in series ten. The series is dated from 1981 to 1996 and is contained in boxes 76 to 106.
Series nine is titled Media and is divided into five subseries. The series contains photographs, slides, negatives, cassettes, CDs and videos relating to planned communities. The series is dated from 1960 to 2004 and contained in boxes 107-232.
Series ten is titled General Information. The information in this series covers a variety of topics relating to planned communities, such as the Department of Housing and Urban Development, newsclippings, Virginia government and other paperwork. The series is dated from 1960 to 2005 and is contained in boxes 233-246.
Series eleven is titled Oversize. This series contains photographs, brochures and posters related to planned communities such as Lake Anne Village Center, Beacon Hill and others. The majority of the series is comprised of architectural drawings, blueprints, floor plans, topography and designs for buildings, such as Reston First Village Center, Reston Town Center and two individual homes, one in Arlington, Virginia and the other in McLean, Virginia. The series is dated from 1960 to 2004 and is contained in boxes 247-351 with additional plans in 3 mapcases.
Arrangement
Organized into 11 series.
Series 1: Reston, 1961-2006 (Boxes 1-42)
Series 2: US Planned Communities, 1970-1996 (Boxes 42-53)
Series 3: International Planned Communities, 1960-1990 (Boxes 53-56)
Series 4: Reports, 1965-2001 (Boxes 56-61)
Series 5: Planned Community Archives Board, 1985-2001 (Boxes 61-64)
Series 6: Promotional Material, 1966-1990 (Boxes 64-66)
Series 7: Brochures, 1990s (Boxes 66-75)
Series 8: Newspapers, 1965-2006 (Boxes 76-106, 242-46, 352-456)
Series 9: Media, 1960-2004 (Boxes 107-232, 348-350)
Series 10: General Information, 1960-2009 (Boxes 233-241)
Series 11: Oversize, 1960-2010 (Boxes 247-347, 351, Mapcase 1-4, Shelf 1-2)
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Special Collections and Archives holds many other collections on the history and development of Reston, Virginia, as well as other collections that document United States and international planned communities.
Alternative Form Available
Selections from the Planned Community Archives are also available in the Reston Planned Community Archives Digital Collection and the Planned Community Archives: Catherine A. Baum Digital Collection.
Index Terms
Persons:
Simon, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1914-; Pennino, Martha, 1918-2004.; Nicoson, William.
Corporate Names:
Planned Community Archives, Inc.
Geographical Names:
Chicago (Ill.); Columbia (Md.); England.; Greenbelt (Md.); Reston (Va.)
Subjects:
Architecture--Designs and plans--United States.; Housing.; Planned communities.
Document Types:
Architectural drawings.; Blueprints.; Elevations.; Floor plans.; Photographic negatives.; Photographic prints.; Slides.
Contents List
- Series 1: Reston, 1961-2006
  The information in this series contains correspondence, finance, plans, reports, meetings, publications, marketing, a scrapbook and general information. All of the information relates to the community of Reston in Virginia.
  - Subseries 1: Correspondence, 1964-1985
    The subseries contains correspondence relating to the development of Reston. The information includes correspondence about the Lake Anne Dam, interoffice correspondence, community facilities and other projects in Reston.
    - Catholic Church-Gulf Reston, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      2.10
    - Community Facilities For Hunters Woods, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Executive Office Stationary and Business Card, 1970s (Box 1, Folder 4)
      19.11
    - Hirst Property, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      3.3
    - Interim Committee, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      7.2
    - Interoffice Correspondence, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      5.3
    - Interoffice Correspondence, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      5.2
    - Interoffice Correspondence, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      5.1
    - Interoffice Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      5.4
    - Interoffice Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      5.5
    - Interoffice Correspondence, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      5.7
    - Interoffice Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      5.6
    - Lake Anne Dam, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      6.2
    - Lake Anne Dam, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      6.3
      - Letter: William C. Cox to Martha Pennino, July 15, 1981; 1.
    - Lake Anne Dam, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      7.1
    - Lake Anne Dam Break Even Analysis, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      7.3
    - Lake Thoreau Dam, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      7.7
    - Letter: Land Purchase by John Hancock Mutual LIfe Certificate of Shares, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      1.12
      - Certificate of Shares - Palindrome Corporation, 17 December 1964; 1.
    - Letter and Proposal: Ralph Segman to Robert Simon, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      480.54
    - Letter to Reston Employees, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      1.13
    - Memorandum and Correspondence on Town Status for Reston, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      13.8
    - Reston Art Gallery, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      477.10
    - Reston Memoranda General Background, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 6)
      499D.01
    - Reston Memoranda Retail Development, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 7)
      499D.02
    - Reston Memoranda Residential Development, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 8)
      499D.03
    - Reston memoranda Industrial Potentials, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 9)
      499D.04
    - Reston Memoranda Industrial Prospects, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 10)
      499D.05
    - Reston Memoranda Airports, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 11)
      499D.06
    - Reston Memoranda Special Projects, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 12)
      499D.07
    - Reston Twentieth Anniversary Committee Correspondence, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      15.1
    - Sale Lease-Back Transaction, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      2.3
    - Transcontinental Gas Pipe Line Corporation, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      2.7
    - Voorhees Study, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      2.9
  - Subseries 2: Finance, 1967-1989
    The information in this subseries is financial information from Reston such as sale agreements, loans, statements and other paperwork relating to the financial aspects of Reston.
    - Amendment to Agree of Sale, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Charles H. Meyers Confidential Budget Report, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      5.11
    - Checking Report, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 19)
      5.13
    - Eurotherm Corporation Section 913 Block 2, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Financial Statements, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      3.14
    - Gulf-Reston "Mobil Reston", 1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      3.15
    - Industrial Land Sales Analysis, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      4.7
    - J.A. Loveless Co. To Reston Land Corporation, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Landscape Maintenance Specifications, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      16.6
    - Land for Sale, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Gordeco-Loans, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      5.9
    - Gulf Reston Properties, Incorporated, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Purchase and Sale of Reston Properties, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Purchase and Sale of Reston Properties, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Purchase and Sale of Reston Properties, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Purchase of Proposed Section 904, Block 2, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Reston Commuter Bus, Incorporated and Reston Interval Bus System, Incorporated Financial Statements, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      13.7
    - Reston Index, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      1.3
    - Reston Park, Incorporated, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      74.1
    - Reston Park, Incorporated, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      74.2
    - Reston Park, Incorporated, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      74.3
    - Transportation Consultants, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - William H. Lauer and Philip S. Hunter, Trustees, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 3: Plans, 1962-1993
    The plans in this subseries are from Reston and include projects such as Reston Town Center, Lake Anne, Reston Twentieth Anniversary Celebrations and others.
    - "A Proposed Form of Inner Government for the New Town of Reston, Virginia" Working Draft, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Corporate Gordeco, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      5.14
    - Kaiser Foundation Health Plan, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Lake Anne Dam Operation, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      7.4
    - Lake Anne and Lake Thoreau, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      6.5
    - Lake Anne and Lake Thoreau, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      6.6
    - North Reston Task Force Phase I Plan, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      16.7
    - Open Space Management and Development-Long Range Plan, 1989-1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      480.50
    - Planning Memoranda on Reston: Report to Simon Enterprises, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      1.1
    - Residential Planned Community Ordinance, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      2.4
    - Residential Planned Community Ordinance, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      2.5
    - Reston Architecture, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      461.29
    - Reston-Commercial Ownership Lake Anne Center, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      645.06
    - Reston Community Center, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      19.15
    - Reston Express Bus, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      4.1
    - Reston Master Plan, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      1.31
    - Reston Town Center Plans, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Reston Town Center-The West Market Neighborhood, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Reston Town Center, Phase II, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Reston Town Center Urban Design Principles, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      645.64
    - Report: Sasaki Associates, Inc., "Reston Town Center Urban Design Principles", February 1991; 1.
    - Reston Twentieth Anniversary Committee, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      15.2
    - Reston: A Symposium; Reston, Virginia, May 8 - 11, 1985; 1.
    - Reston Twentieth Anniversary Committee-Planning Notes, 1980s (Box 10, Folder 1)
      15.3
    - Shadowwood Project, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      3.6
    - Simon Enterprise Developers, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      1.2
    - Site Development-Design Criteria, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      5.8
    - Social Planning and Programs, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      19.6
    - Social Planning and Programs for Reston, Virginia, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      480.53
  - Subseries 4: Reports, 1966-1994
    The subseries has reports relating to projects in Reston. The reports contain information from projects such as housing community developments, schools, health clubs, Lake Anne, Lake Thoreau and other projects in Reston.
    - "Affordable Housing for Low and Moderate Income Families in Reston", 1984 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      12.15
    - Analysis-Ashley Court, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Analysis-Ced Hollow, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Analysis-Lake Audubon Terrace, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Analysis-Oak Spring, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Appraisal Report of 3730 Acres Land, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      4.4
    - Chapter VI: Community Planning, Washington Research Center-Reston Report, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      12.4
    - Chapter VI: Negotiating With the Federal Government, Washington Research Center-Reston Report, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      12.5
    - Chapter VIII: Land Development and First Construction, Washington Research Center-Reston Report, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      12.6
    - Chapter IX: Financing Reston, Washington Research Center-Reston Report, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      12.7
    - Chapter X: Industrial and Commercial Development, Washington Research Center-Reston Report, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      12.8
    - Chapter XI: Reston and the Public, Washington Research Center-Reston Report, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      12.9
    - Declaration of Covenants, Conditions and Restrictions, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Dedication of Reston Program, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      1.6
    - Deed of Dedication, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      1.5
    - "Environmental Management and the Reston Homeowners" by Gene S. Bergoffen, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      18.3
    - "Gordeco" by Peter G. Miller, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      4.3
    - Gulf-Reston Schools, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      2.11
    - Gulf-Reston Miscellaneous Studies, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      2.12
    - Health Club, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      2.8
    - House Settlement Study, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      3.5
    - Jane G. Wilhelm for Reston Symposium-Paper, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      18.6
    - John Hancock Land, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      3.7
    - Geotechnical Engineering Report-Stability Analysis Lake Anne Dam, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      4.14
    - Lake Anne Dam, Phase II Inspection Report, 1980s (Box 11, Folder 13)
      4.13
    - Lake Anne Dam-Inspection Report, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      6.1
    - Lake and Dam Study, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      2.6
    - Lake Thoreau Dam, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      7.5
    - Lake Thoreau Dam, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      7.6
    - Oak Park Case Study, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - O and R Study, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      3.4
    - Report on Reston Density Control, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      18.4
    - Report of Reston-Foundation for Community Programs, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      480.20
    - Report-Reston Industrial Center, 1970s (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Reston Industrial Center, ca. 1967; 1.
    - Report to the Reston Community on Governance Options, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      480.52
    - Report to Reston Land Corporation (Market Planning STudy for Hotel Development in Reston Town Center), 1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Reports-New Planned Communities, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Reports-New Planned Communities, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Reports-New Planned Communities, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Residential Market Study for Phase 4 of Reston Town Center, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Reston Town Center By-laws, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Reston: A Symposium, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      15.5
    - Reston Center for Industry and Government Declaration of Protective Covenants and Restrictions, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      1.7
    - Reston: Density Control Under the Residential Planned Community, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      3.1
    - Reston How Income Housing Demonstration Program, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      480.2
    - Reston Report-Washington Research Center Chapter V-Legal Organization, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      12.3
    - "Reston: The Answers to the Problem of the City" by Brennan, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      13.5
    - Social Planning and Programs for Reston, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      543.8
    - Technology and Culture in Perspective, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      19.5
    - The Need for a Community Friend in a New Town, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      19.7
  - Subseries 5: Meetings, 1964-2000
    The information in this series contains material from the transportation committee, board meeting minutes and other meeting information in Reston.
    - Combined Board Meeting of Gulf Oil Real Estate, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      3.8
    - Gulf Oil Corporation, Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      2.2
    - Gulf Oil Corporation Index to Board Minutes, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      2.1
    - Gulf Oil Corporation Presentation of the Real Estate Strategy Center to the Chairman's Advisory Council, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      4.10
    - Gulf-Reston Lepage/Caldwell, Banker, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      3.13
    - Staff Meeting, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      3.2
    - Transportation Committee, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Transportation Committee, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Transportation Committee, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 6: Publications, 1964-2006
    The subseries contains publications from Reston or about Reston such as the Restonian Magazine, The Reston Letter, The Reston Times and The Washington Post. Some of the documents are a complete copy of the publication, other documents are only articles from the publications.
    - A Billion Dollar Be on a New Way To Live-Look Magazine, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      10.9
    - A Brief History of Reston, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      12.2
    - "A Summer Festival for Talented Young, Musicians: The Proposal for the Reston Music Center, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      9.12
    - "A Mission to Serve: The Life of John A Scherzer" (2 copies), 1989 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      10.27
    - Action, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      247.30
    - Architecture Firm First to Lease at Two Fountain Square, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      648.15
    - Article-"They Were Here Before, Bob Simon", 1985 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      10.24
    - Bringing Downtown to a Lackluster New Town Warfield's, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      648.06
    - "Commonwealth" Reston-A New Town for a New King of Life, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      10.11
    - Community Hall Bulletin: Lake Anne, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      19.8
    - Copies of Reston Related News, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Courier Journal: Reston, Virginia-Planned Community Aborning, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      10.10
    - Creating the Great Society, The New Republic: "America Tomorrow", 1964 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      10.8
    - Downtown Reston Town Center, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      648.24
    - Environmental Management Committee, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      13.4
    - Family Circle, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      10.18
    - Handbooks, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - "Help Wanted" at Town Center, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      648.11
    - House and Garden, "The Lure of Living in Clustered Housing", 1967 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      10.16
    - Identity, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      647.08
    - "Indicators of Change", 2003 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Industrial Design: "Brave New Town", 1964 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      10.5
      - Article: Edward Carpenter, "Brave New Town," Industrial Design, March 1964; 1.
    - "It's Christmastime in the City", 1990s (Box 16, Folder 8)
      648.23
    - Local Amenities, 1990s (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Loundoun County, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Mobil World, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      247.29
    - Molson USA Plans to Move to Reston-Washington Post, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      648.16
    - Movies Munchies at Town Center-Fairfax Journal, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      648.18
    - New Downtown Wows-Fairfax Journal, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      648.08
    - New Republic-"50th Anniversary Issue-America Tomorrow Creating the Great Society", 1964 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      19.2
    - New Towns-Articles, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - New Towns-Articles, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      13.3
    - New Towns-Reston and Others Clippings, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      13.2